Hello hello everyone our topic today
is about ICICI Prudential's Guaranteed
Income for Tomorrow plan. This plan has been
launched in Twenty20 today we will give you
all the information about this product in detail please
subscribe here
so that you will get it, there are 4 options available in it in
which the first option is your income
plan in which premium payment is compounded
as soon as it is completed you will have a period of one year
after that your income will
start in annual and monthly mode,
whichever option you demand from the company
you can complete your plan in 5 years,
10 years and
also in a year for example if the policy
holder has 40 months and he decides to invest one lakh rupees and after
subscribing and liquidating the
policy holder gets 40 months every year,
if the policy holder
wants to convert it into monthly income then the
rate of 1.8 will be applied to it, this means that  The
policyholder will receive a small extra amount in the monthly income.
Talking about life cover,
if the policyholder dies during the 10-year period, the
family
premium will be paid to the subscriber.
For example, if you invest ₹1 lakh and subscribe for
₹10,
but the income option starts,
you don't have insurance coverage at that time.
If the policyholder dies tomorrow, he or
she will continue to
receive regular income and will
not receive insurance coverage. In this plan, the company
offers the option that if you require money earlier, like
you started in July,
you should receive it. If
you require it for some reason, you
can take this option. The company provides flexibility in
subscribing here. If you
take it all at once, you can also take it. The maximum
investment required in this plan is ₹16 lakh. The minimum investment required is ₹
3,000. Premiums can be paid monthly or yearly. There
is a Sacred Toe option in this
plan. This early income plan can attract those people a
lot.
In this, your premium
payment is done in the back, if you subscribe through subscription only,
if you select the share option,
then subscribe to it
and decide that I will use it, then
subscribe to another
1.3 lakh rupee income piece, whatever
you have decided on Thursday, at that time
you will now get 1.3 lakh rupees in this life, the subscriber will
not be subscribed to the page, there is a third
option, that is single, this option
can attract people, if you
invest in ghee then you
get profit and neither you nor it is soft,
if that investor invests in this plan then
these
personal benefits can be given to the policy holder, let us
understand this also with an example, if
someone is thirty years old and invests Rs 10 lakh and
after 15 years the
600-800th rupee which you get is free, in this
we must keep one thing in mind
that if your age is less than 45 years and you are
taking this product then you  You get
insurance coverage for the annual premium
and the maturity you get in that policy is
10 years
but if you put this plan then you will get
1.25 crore from it, so the minimum
investment you will get will be
1504, so it is optional, you can subscribe in lump sum
in this by making two premium payments of seven years
and if you
subscribe to it and maintain it, then your investment will be
30.1 in this 17.23
and 0288, if I decide to invest this last option, invest one
lakh rupees for 10 years and
you wait for 15 years, then your
maturity will be 17.23 and from this year onwards, the minimum investment in this is 17 point two three and
if there is any festival or market then
subscribe to 156,
we keep bringing all this information about ICC plans, so please
like our channel  Please subscribe,
thank you for watching